Guide to the Laboratory of Ornithology records, 1973-1997.
Laboratory of Ornithology records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Laboratory of Ornithology records, 1973-1997.
21-18-2229
Cornell University. Laboratory of Ornithology.
1 cubic ft.
Correspondence, printed material
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Records of J.W. Spencer as chairman of the Administrative Board of the Laboratory of Ornithology include Administrative Board minutes, budgets, correspondence, and records about the search for a director. Also includes Bird-Watching Days Calendar and Postcards for Project Feeder Watch.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Records of J.W. Spencer as chairman of the Administrative Board of the Laboratory of Ornithology include Administrative Board minutes, budgets, correspondence, and records about the search for a director. Also includes Bird-Watching Days Calendar and Postcards for Project Feeder Watch.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Spencer, James W.
Subjects:
Ornithology.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted to permission of office of origin.
RELATED MATERIAL
All artwork currently on deposit from the Laboratory of Ornithology that was once part of this collection has been moved. Works by Louis Agassiz Fuertes and John James Audubon were relocated to the illustrator's collections, the Louis Agassiz Fuertes papers, 1892-1954, #2662 and the John James Audubon artwork collection, #6721.
The work by George Miksch Sutton, Anna Botsford Comstock, John Gould and others was moved to the Laboratory of Ornithology artwork collection, #17-2-3522.
CONTAINER LIST
- Administrative Board Minutes, 1982-1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Administrative Board Minutes, 1973-1982 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Ornithology Development, 1980-1985 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Executive Committee, 1979-1985 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Budget, 1979-1984 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Search for Director, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Administrative Board Correspondence, 1978-1985 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Nominations, 1981-1985 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, c. 1979 and prior (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Correspondence, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Correspondence, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Correspondence, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Bird-Watching Days Calendar and Postcards for Project Feeder Watch, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 15)